<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RajReni Kaul</title>
    <link>https://renikaul.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on RajReni Kaul</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://renikaul.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum vitae</title>
      <link>https://renikaul.github.io/blogs/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renikaul.github.io/blogs/cv/</guid>
      <description>Download my full CV in pdf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Science for all</title>
      <link>https://renikaul.github.io/blogs/outreach/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:42:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renikaul.github.io/blogs/outreach/</guid>
      <description>On April 22, 2017 I headed out to the Athens March for Science, while UGA Dawgs headed to Stanford stadium for the annual spring scrimmage football game. I saw this as a missed opportunity to bring together these two UGA-loving groups. This inspired me to launch STEMzone, an outreach organization that facilitates UGA STEM researchers communication with the broader Athens/UGA community during football tailgating (Read more about my inspiration and the first event).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Launching STEMzone</title>
      <link>https://renikaul.github.io/blogs/launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renikaul.github.io/blogs/launch/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve written a &amp;ldquo;how to&amp;rdquo; guide to launch STEMzone at your university. Please contact me, or the current e-board, if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in starting this event at your University. I have plenty of lessons learned to share!
  Recruitment poster presented virtually at the Ecological Society of America 2020.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://renikaul.github.io/blogs/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renikaul.github.io/blogs/teaching/</guid>
      <description>My complete teaching portfolio.
Other related projects Group effort to make Marcus Zokan&amp;rsquo;s amazing dataset more accessible while learning javascript. http://zooplankton.ecology.uga.edu/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Road to Extinction</title>
      <link>https://renikaul.github.io/blogs/dissertation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renikaul.github.io/blogs/dissertation/</guid>
      <description>My dissertation research focuses on population ecology, spanning from theoretical to applied. I am interested in the general path populations take on the road to extinction. Theoreticians have developed models that capture what we think that road looks like. My work pushes these ideas forward by trying to re-create this theoretical road in a highly controlled laboratory setting. This work acts as a proof of concept before exploring these ideas in (an often messy) natural setting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>https://renikaul.github.io/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renikaul.github.io/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predicting disease dynamics</title>
      <link>https://renikaul.github.io/blogs/disease/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renikaul.github.io/blogs/disease/</guid>
      <description>I have a wide range of scientific interests, and enjoy collaborating with my Drake labmates. This has led to many projects that involve some combination of disease dynamics, machine learning, and modeling. Here are a few highlights.
Yellow fever in Brazil Explore the project&amp;rsquo;s [workflow on github].
The spread of yellow fever into areas previously thought of as low risk presented an ecologically interesting question- what’s changed about the disease dynamics in the region, and an important question for human health- can we predict areas of high risk for the disease.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>